(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
えー、皆様、本日は轟はじめ生誕祭2025にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Umm, everyone, thank you very much for coming to the Todoroki Hajime Birthday Festival 2025 today.
開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the performance, I would like to make some requests and announcements.
当配信は一部収録を含みますが、生配信部分もございますので、いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください。
This stream includes some pre-recorded segments, but there are also live broadcast parts, so please comment a lot and get excited.
マニマニも見えてるんでしゅけど... うんちょ、うんちょ、番長！
I can see the 'Manimani' as well... Uncho, uncho, Bancho!
きゃー！きちゃー！おー、きちゃー！
Kyaa! It's here! Oh, it's here!
おー、やべえ。こんちくわー。ありがとうございましゅ。
Oh, man. Konchikuwa! Thank you very much.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前での飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないようにお気をつけください。
Eating and drinking in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone is allowed, but please be careful not to spill on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは「轟はじめ生誕祭2025」でしゅ。
The hashtag for this stream is #TodorokiHajimeBirthdayFestival2025.
SNSでたくさんポストしてくだちゃい。
Please post a lot on social media.
開演中、パソコンやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影、大歓迎でしゅ。
Taking photos with your PC or smartphone during the performance is very welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上げてくれると、うれちいしゅ。
I'd be happy if you post a lot and help liven things up.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちくだちゃい。
Now, please wait a little longer until the performance begins.
えー、皆様、本日は轟はじめ生誕祭2025にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Umm, everyone, thank you very much for coming to the Todoroki Hajime Birthday Festival 2025 today.
開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the performance, I would like to make some requests and announcements.
えー、当配信は一部収録を含みますが、生配信部分もございますので、いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてくれると、すごくうれちいしゅ。
Umm, this stream includes some pre-recorded segments, but there are also live broadcast parts, so I'd be very happy if you comment a lot and get excited.
じょわ、じょわ。2周目助かる。ワクワク。2回目。いいだろう、2回言っても。ありがとね。
Jowa, jowa. Second lap helps! How exciting. A second time. It's fine to say it twice, right? Thanks.
えー、テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前での飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないようにお気をつけください。
Umm, eating and drinking in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone is allowed, but please be careful not to spill on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは「轟はじめ生誕祭2025」でしゅ。
The hashtag for this stream is #TodorokiHajimeBirthdayFestival2025.
SNSでたくさんポストしてくだちゃい。
Please post a lot on social media.
開演中、パソコンやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影も、あの、大歓迎なので、いっぱいいっぱいいっぱい、いっぱいポストしてくだちゃい。
During the performance, photography by PC or smartphone is also, uh, very welcome, so please post many, many, many, many times.
それでは、開演までしばらく、もうちょっと、お待ちくだちゃい。
Now, please wait a little longer, just a bit more, until the performance begins.
KAMIKAZE
作詞・作曲：マサ
Lyrics & Composition: Masa
震えとったな
You were shaking, weren't you?
謝っても無駄
Apologizing is useless
何がしたいか分からん
I don't know what you want to do
もううんざりだ
I'm sick of it
ばかばっかだ全く
Seriously, everyone's a fool
ああ 息苦しい世界だわ
Ah, it's a suffocating world
1 2 3 からカウント
Count from 1, 2, 3
シャイなバーテン ゾンビに頼んだ
The shy bartender asked a zombie
まやかし証しのシロップはビター
The syrup of deception is bitter
天然物です ビタンサン
It's all natural, slightly sparkling
暴れる準備は決まって
Preparation for going wild is set
派手なイントロダクション唸った
The flashy introduction roared
夢のパーティーが始まった
The dream party has begun
あかんべーのベー また ベーベーベー
Sticking out my tongue, again, bleh bleh bleh
うるさい めんどくさいなもう アイアイアイヤイヤイヤ
Noisy, annoying, enough, ay ay ay-ya ya ya
おー あかんべーのベー また ベーベーベー
Oh, sticking out my tongue, again, bleh bleh bleh
興醒め 関わんなよ 怠いだけ
What a killjoy, don't involve me, it's just tiresome
おー 揺れる 揺れる スィンギン
Oh, swaying, swaying, swingin'
圧倒的な旋律
An overwhelming melody
まだまだ踊ってよ ご愁傷様
Keep on dancing, my condolences
おー 揺れる 揺れる スィンギン
Oh, swaying, swaying, swingin'
圧倒的な旋律
An overwhelming melody
ダラダッタ ララダッタ ララダッタ ラララ
Dara-datta rara-datta rara-datta rara-ra
清廉潔白 私の過去には 何の過ちもございません
With a clean slate, there are no mistakes in my past
分厚くなってくルールブック 見逃した時には万事休す
The rulebook keeps getting thicker, miss a detail and it's all over
ビックリ精度のサーチライト 「それはやばいよ」が一番怖いよ
A searchlight with amazing precision, 'That's bad' is the scariest thing
レッドもイエローも関係ないのよ 一発退場！
Red or yellow doesn't matter, immediate ejection!
はい、お疲れシャン
Right, good job then
1 2 3 からカウント
Count from 1, 2, 3
熱いロックンロールを喰らった
I was hit by hot rock 'n' roll
インターリュードにのぼせてビナー
Flushed during the interlude, Vina
晩ギャのゾンビもバラバ
The band-girl zombies are scattered too
アイドルタイムも終わって
Idol time is over too
あっという間にこっから終盤だぞ
In the blink of an eye, we're in the final stretch
ゾンビもネコも杓子も 踊ってるだけ
Zombies and everyone else, they're all just dancing
あかんべーのベー また ベーベーベー
Sticking out my tongue, again, bleh bleh bleh
うるさい めんどくさいなもう アイアイアイヤイヤイヤ
Noisy, annoying, enough, ay ay ay-ya ya ya
おー あかんべーのベー また ベーベーベー
Oh, sticking out my tongue, again, bleh bleh bleh
興醒め 関わんなよ 怠いだけ
What a killjoy, don't involve me, it's just tiresome
おー 揺れる 揺れる スィンギン
Oh, swaying, swaying, swingin'
圧倒的な旋律
An overwhelming melody
まだまだ踊ってよ ご愁傷様
Keep on dancing, my condolences
おー 揺れる 揺れる スィンギン
Oh, swaying, swaying, swingin'
圧倒的な旋律
An overwhelming melody
ダラダッタ ララダッタ ララダッタ ラララ
Dara-datta rara-datta rara-datta rara-ra
おー あかんべーのベー また ベーベーベー
Oh, sticking out my tongue, again, bleh bleh bleh
うるさい めんどくさいなもう アイアイアイヤイヤイヤ
Noisy, annoying, enough, ay ay ay-ya ya ya
おー あかんべーのベー また ベーベーベー
Oh, sticking out my tongue, again, bleh bleh bleh
興醒め 関わんなよ 怠いだけ
What a killjoy, don't involve me, it's just tiresome
おー 揺れる 揺れる スィンギン
Oh, swaying, swaying, swingin'
圧倒的な旋律
An overwhelming melody
まだまだ踊ってよ ご愁傷様
Keep on dancing, my condolences
おー 揺れる 揺れる スィンギン
Oh, swaying, swaying, swingin'
圧倒的な旋律
An overwhelming melody
ダラダッタ ララダッタ ララダッタ ラララ
Dara-datta rara-datta rara-datta rara-ra
まだまだ割れるけど
It's still breaking apart, but
ベーベーベー 死なないで
Bleh bleh bleh, please don't die
OFFSIDE
作詞・作曲：マサ
Lyrics & Composition: Masa
なんだか急がしく笑うテンポ
A tempo that laughs somewhat busily
街中がバラバラ
The whole town is in pieces
暴れたゾンビとロックスター
Rampaging zombies and rock stars
退場都市ガレージ
Exit City Garage
空から撃ち抜くバニーガール
A bunny girl shooting from the sky
騒いでる様々
Everyone is making a fuss
現れた近所のバランサー
The neighborhood balancer appeared
笑った確信とスーサイド
Laughed with certainty and suicide
この惨状たたき台で
With this tragic state as a draft
まだまだいけるか？
Can you still go on?
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
When the chime of a happy ending
想像通りじゃないなら
isn't quite what you imagined,
塗り替えてしまうのさ
just paint over it.
ゆらゆらゆらゆらどうぞ
Swaying, swaying, swaying, come on.
敗北感とは
A sense of defeat isn't
分かち合うもんではないから
something to be shared,
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
so kick it away and dye it your color.
そんなもんさ
That's just how it is.
正直こんなの
To be honest,
意味あるのかって
I wonder if there's any point to this,
考えたところで 堂々巡りで
but thinking about it just goes in circles.
あれも これも それも気になる
That, this, and even that bother me.
気になる 気になる
It bothers me, it bothers me.
それぞれ描いた 正義が絡み合う
The different justices we've envisioned intertwine.
あぁ まだまだ 行けそうさ
Ah, I can still keep going.
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
When the chime of a happy ending
想像通りじゃないなら
isn't quite what you imagined,
塗り替えてしまうのさ
just paint over it.
ゆらゆらゆらゆらどうぞ
Swaying, swaying, swaying, come on.
敗北感とは
A sense of defeat isn't
分かち合うもんではないから
something to be shared,
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
so kick it away and dye it your color.
そんなもんさ
That's just how it is.
どこで何が起きるか分からない
I don't know what will happen where.
またやり直せるかな
I wonder if I can start over again.
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
When the chime of a happy ending
想像通りじゃないなら
isn't quite what you imagined,
塗り替えてしまうのさ
just paint over it.
ゆらゆらゆらゆらどうぞ
Swaying, swaying, swaying, come on.
敗北感とは
A sense of defeat isn't
分かち合うもんではないから
something to be shared,
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
so kick it away and dye it your color.
そんなもんさ
That's just how it is.
はぁー、いやぁー、はぁ、
Haa... Whew... Haa...
皆さーん、こんちくわー！
Everyone, Kon-chikuwa!
はじめの第一回生誕祭、来てくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming to Hajime's very first birthday celebration.
#はしたご は、轟はじめ生誕祭2025です！
#Hashitago is the Hajime Todoroki Birthday Festival 2025!
たくさんポストしてくれて嬉しい！
I'm so happy you're all posting so much!
アニョー！トレンド入ってるー！
Whoa! It's trending!
ありがとうございます！嬉しい！
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
本日は、アニョー、すごい、
Today, whoa, it's amazing.
色んなはじめをお届けするので、
I'll be showing you many different sides of Hajime,
ぜひポストしてくれると嬉しいれす。
so I'd be glad if you keep posting.
先ほどは「神風」と「OFFSIDE」という曲を聞いていただきました。
You just heard the songs 'Kamikaze' and 'OFFSIDE'.
どうでしたかー？
How was it?
かっこよかったですかー？
Was it cool?
「かっこよかったよー！」
'It was so cool!'
ありがとありがと。ありがとねー。
Thank you, thank you. Thank you.
はじめは曲もね、この振り付けもめちゃくちゃ大好きなので、
Hajime loves these songs and the choreography so much,
めちゃくちゃ披露できて嬉しいれす！
that I'm thrilled to be able to perform them for you!
この後もまだたくさんあるので、
There's still a lot more to come,
一緒に楽しんでくださーい。
so please enjoy it with me.
次は、今かっこよかったけど、
Next up, that was cool, but
セクシーパートれす！
it's time for the sexy part!
おおー！それでは、いきましょう。
Ooh! All right then, let's go.
One, two, one...
Wow!
Deal with the devil
作詞・作曲：ryo (supercell)
Lyrics & Composition: ryo (supercell)
Up down 世の常
Up and down, it's the way of the world
崩した一丁あがりの勝負
Breaking down, a match decided in one go
肝心なのはストロングなマイマインド
What's vital is a strong mind of my own
出し抜いてさあ
So, outsmart them
行きつく先は ヘブン or ヘル
The destination is heaven or hell
この世界のルール たった一つ
There's only one rule in this world
勝者こそが正義
The winner is justice
女は度胸
A woman needs courage
焦らさせるのよ あいつを
I'll make him impatient
やれること何だってやるわ
I'll do whatever it takes
私は賭け狂いのクイーン
I am the gambling-obsessed queen
網膜に映る闇切って
Cutting through the darkness reflected in my retinas
連勝 どう？
Consecutive wins, how's that?
デビルさぁ目を見透かして
Devil, see through my eyes
私のものにする
I'll make it all mine
あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Down to every single strand of your hair
How many you die? I select.
震えてるわよ 坊や
You're trembling, boy
降ろしはしないわ
I won't let you fold
デビルさぁ面倒温存じゃ
Devil, if I just save face,
たまらないわ スリル
the thrill won't be enough
誰にも触らせない黒真珠
Black pearl that I'll let no one touch
How many you die? I select.
さあ来な
Now, come on
...覚悟決めて
...prepare yourself.
震えて溢れ My heart
My heart is trembling and overflowing.
欲しがるようじゃね まだベイビー
If you're still wanting more, you're still a baby.
誰にも負けない 感情させて Let me Honey
Let me feel an emotion second to none, let me, honey.
あなた 内緒だわ
You, it's a secret.
ほら見せてあげる
See, I'll show you.
秘密って甘いもの
Secrets are sweet things.
仕掛けて 罠に嵌めるわ
I'll set it up and trap you.
油断誘うのよ
Luring you into carelessness.
思考を止めたら 終末 (ジ・エンド)
If you stop thinking, it's the end.
何も知らないような顔で落とすわ 鼻先を
I'll make you fall with a face that knows nothing... right under your nose.
急かせる所じゃない？
Isn't it time to hurry?
読み切って 連鎖だ
Read it all, it's a chain reaction.
デッド・オア・アライヴ 見逃さない
Dead or alive, I won't miss a thing.
どんな小さなズルだって
No matter how small the trick...
アタシの目は誤魔化されないわ
...my eyes won't be deceived.
A million dollars 愛されちゃいたいわ 骨まで
A million dollars, I want to be loved to the bone.
愛し尽くしてあげる
I'll love you with everything I have.
狙った獲物は逃さない
I won't let the target escape.
唇濡らして 頂くわ My babe
Wetting my lips, I'll take it, my babe.
ダイヤのジャックで 出揃うわ
With the jack of diamonds, the hand is complete.
笑みを殺し 待つだけ
Killing the smile, just waiting.
アタシのポーカーフェイスは いつでもパーフェクト
My poker face is always perfect.
一部の隙も見せたりしないわ
I won't show even a single opening.
深淵感じてるわ
I'm feeling the abyss.
お望みなら 最期まで
If you wish, until the very end.
見てばかりいないで 荒らして
Don't just watch, go wild.
いかせてはくれない
You won't let me go.
負けるのが怖い？ 弱いチキン
Scared to lose? You weak chicken.
読み切って連鎖だ
Read it all, it's a chain reaction.
デッド・オア・アライヴ 見透かして
Dead or alive, see through it.
アタシのものにする
I'll make you mine.
あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Every single hair of yours.
A million dollars 愛されちゃいたいわ 震えてるわボーヤ
A million dollars, I want to be loved, you're trembling, boy.
どこまで行くわ
I'll go anywhere.
デッド・オア・アライヴ 昂ぶって堪らないわ
Dead or alive, the excitement is unbearable.
スリル 誰にも触らせない
The thrill, I won't let anyone touch it.
この真似
Like this...
A million dollars 愛されちゃいたいわ さあカモン覚悟決めて
A million dollars, I want to be loved, come on, prepare yourself.
灰になるまで撃って
Shoot until I turn to ash.
欲しがるようじゃね まだベイビー
If you're still wanting more, you're still a baby.
誰にも負けない 感情させて Let me Honey
Let me feel an emotion second to none, let me, honey.
丸ノ内サディスティック
Marunouchi Sadistic
作詞・作曲：椎名林檎
Written and Composed by Sheena Ringo
報酬は入社後 並行線で
The reward will be after joining, on parallel lines.
東京は愛せど 何も無い
Even though I love Tokyo, it has nothing.
リッケン620頂戴
Give me a Rickenbacker 620.
19万も持って居ない
I don't even have 190,000 yen.
お茶の水
Ochanomizu
マーシャルの匂いで飛んじゃって大変さ
Flying off with the smell of Marshall, it's trouble.
毎晩絶頂に達して居るだけさ
Just reaching a climax every night.
ラット一つを商売道具にしているさ
Using one Rat as my business tool.
そしたらベンジーが肺に写ってトリップ
Then Benjie is reflected in my lungs, and I trip.
警官ごっこ
Playing cop
国境は越えても
Even if I cross the border
盛者必衰
The prosperous must decline
領収書書いて頂戴
Please write me a receipt
税理士なんて就いていない
I don't have a tax accountant
後楽園
Kourakuen
将来僧になって結婚して欲しい
I want you to become a monk and marry me in the future
毎晩寝具で遊戯するだけ
Just playing in bed every night
ピザ屋の彼女になってみたい
I want to try being a pizza delivery girl's girlfriend
そしたらベンジー、あたしをグレッチで殴って
Then Benjie, hit me with your Gretsch
青噛んでいって頂戴
Please keep chewing the blue
終電で帰るてば池袋
Returning by the last train to Ikebukuro
マーシャルの匂いで飛んじゃって大変さ
It's crazy, flying high on the smell of Marshall
毎晩絶頂に達しているだけ
Just reaching a climax every night
ラットひとつ商売道具にしているさ
I'm using a single RAT as my tool of the trade
そしたらベンジーが肺に写ってトリップ
Then Benjie is reflected in my lungs and I'm tripping
将来僧になって結婚して欲しい
I want you to become a monk and marry me in the future
毎晩寝具で遊戯するだけ
Just playing in bed every night
ピザ屋の彼女になってみたい
I want to try being a pizza delivery girl's girlfriend
そしたらベンジー、あたしをグレッチで殴って
Then Benjie, hit me with your Gretsch
はい！
Yes!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
次は、ゲストパートです！
Next is the guest part!
今日も元気にドカンを決めたらヨーラン背負ってリーゼント
Today too, I'm energetic in my baggy pants, wearing my long jacket and pompadour
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Delinquent High School Rock'n Roll
ソリも入れたし弁当持ったし
Got my side shaved and my lunchbox ready
可愛いあの娘はくるくるパーマに長めのスカート引きずって
That cute girl has curly permed hair and drags her long skirt along
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Delinquent High School Rock'n Roll
お手々つないで駅までしあわせ
Holding hands until the station, so happy
駅についたらドッパい兄ちゃんとガンくらべ合い飛ばし合い
Arriving at the station, staring down and trading glares with the flashy guys
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Delinquent High School Rock'n Roll
タイマンはりましょ赤テープ同士で
Let's have a one-on-one between red-tape holders
かあちゃん、そんなに心配すんなよ。
Mom, don't worry so much.
勉強嫌いな俺らだけどさ、
We might hate studying, but
人にはそれぞれ合った道ってもんがあんねん。
everyone has a path that suits them.
もっと優しく大きな愛で、言わぬが僕の沈丁花。
With a gentler, greater love, my unspoken daphne flower.
何だよおっかあ、あそこにマブい女いるじゃんよ。
What's up, Mom? There's a hot girl over there.
どっちの男連れてんの？
Which guy is she with?
おや、羅天じゃない。
Oh, isn't that Raden?
あでゃ、らでぃんじゃない？
Oh, isn't that Radin?
電車に乗ったら便所に駆け込み 一駅だけのハッピータイム
Boarding the train, rushing to the toilet for a one-station happy time
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Delinquent High School Rock'n Roll
火のないところに煙を立てて
Raising smoke where there is no fire
電車を飛び降り改札抜けたら 学校まではもうダッシュ
Jumping off the train, passing through the gate, it's a dash to school
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Delinquent High School Rock'n Roll
またまた遅刻で今日も呼び出し
Late again, getting called in today too
サンキュー！
Thank you!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thanks for coming!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！バイバイ！
Thank you very much! Bye-bye!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
バレる！
It's gonna be exposed!
Oh yeah ちょっと待って 何これ 知らぬ間に変わり果て
Oh yeah, wait a second, what's this? It's completely changed before I knew it.
Oh yeah どこにも見当たらない人の足跡
Oh yeah, I can't find any human footprints anywhere.
胸の高鳴り抑え 送り込む肺に酸素
Suppresses the throbbing of the chest, sending oxygen to the lungs.
また増え ハイリスクな残響 有為の八木八光
Increasing again, high-risk reverberations, Yagi Hakko's significance.
Who's next? 次は誰が描き出す画期的な自画像
Who's next? Who will draw the next groundbreaking self-portrait?
数多の屍かき分け誰もが血眼
Pushing through countless corpses, everyone is bloodshot.
上も下もパンパンな末期的な地獄から吸い
Sucking from the terminal hell where both top and bottom are packed.
前人未踏 現れ見せつける加えた力
Unprecedented, appearing and showing off the added strength.
さばく付いたあの老いぼれ 邪魔ならそこどいとけ
That old man with a grudge, if you're in the way, move it.
白昼の打ち勝て 百戦錬磨の呼び声
Overcome the broad daylight, the call of the battle-hardened.
Oh yeah えげつないもの発明したのかも
Oh yeah, I might have invented something nasty.
生中継 革命前夜 歓喜しとのラボ
Live broadcast, the eve of the revolution, the lab with joy.
ばれる はっ この俺の天賦の才が
It's gonna get out, ha! This natural talent of mine.
ばれる おっ まじこれめんどくさいな
It's gonna get out, oh, this is really annoying.
ばれる はっ ばれる えい
It's gonna get out, ha! It's gonna get out, hey!
世の中に気づかれる
The world is going to notice.
Let's go 吠え面かきな Oh my haters
Let's go, cry your eyes out, oh my haters.
とりあえず浴びるわ拍手
For now, I'll just soak up the applause.
ほら見たことか にやけろ
See, I told you so! Now grin.
Oh yeah 拍手と歓声 ここ日の当たる場所
Oh yeah, applause and cheers, this is the place in the sun.
沈着冷静 地に足つけたままありがとう
Calm and composed, with my feet on the ground, thank you.
地名も名声も水物 勝つパンドラの箱
Both local names and fame are fleeting, a winning Pandora's box.
頭でわかっちゃいるくせに あぁ身体がまじで行くミステリー
Even though I understand it in my head, ah, my body really goes, it's a mystery.
あの嬌声に群がるサビ 影響を免れぬ椅子取りゲーム
The rust that swarms to those shrill voices, a game of musical chairs that can't escape influence.
一度のミス買い戻したれ 胸の手の平返して一斉に
Buy back that one mistake, flip your hand over your chest all at once.
白黒つけられないもう捨てちまえ時代遅れの
Can't distinguish black and white, just throw away the outdated...
失うものが欲しい 欲しい 欲しい 欲しい
I want something to lose, want it, want it, want it.
俺をわかってくれと叫べ世に知らしめたばかりに
Shouting 'Understand me!' just because I let the world know.
自分で自分をより自分らしく演じなきゃいけない羽目に
I ended up having to play myself more like myself.
求められてるあの味 でも俺はもうそこにはない
That taste that's being sought, but I'm no longer there.
俺って誰 俺って何 ビビって手も足も出ないぜ
Who am I? What am I? I'm so scared I can't do a thing.
ばれる はっ 俺にはもう何にもない
It's gonna get out, ha! I have nothing left.
ばれる はっ 初めから勘違いだった
It's gonna get out, ha! It was a misunderstanding from the start.
ばれる はっ ばれる えい
It's gonna get out, ha! It's gonna get out, hey!
化けの皮剥がされる
The disguise is going to be stripped away.
Let's go 見添えちゃおう my haters
Let's go, let's keep an eye on them, my haters.
手を叩いて指差して
Clap your hands and point your finger.
ほら見たことか 笑える
See, I told you so! It's funny.
生きてる限りは勝ち逃げできねぇな
As long as you're alive, you can't get away with it.
衰え錆びつき同化されてしまう定めか
Is it fate to be withered, rusted, and assimilated?
メッキ剥いだのは 熱病書いたのは
The one who stripped the plating, the one who wrote the fever...
あの日の俺とよく似た目をしてたやつでした
It was someone who had eyes very similar to mine back then.
生憎俺はまだ渡れぬ三途の川
Unfortunately, I still can't cross the Sanzu River.
今日もまた積み上げては蹴飛ばされる賽の河原
Even today, it's the riverbed of Sai, where you build it up only to have it kicked down.
瞳孔が見開いた 逃げ場と微笑んだ
My pupils dilated, I smiled as a way out.
喉元しのばせる刀とあとな引き金
A sword hidden at the throat and then the trigger.
ばれる はっ この俺の天賦の才が
It's gonna get out, ha! This natural talent of mine.
ばれる おっ まじこれめんどくさいな
It's gonna get out, oh, this is really annoying.
ばれる はっ ばれる えい
It's gonna get out, ha! It's gonna get out, hey!
世の中に気づかれる
The world is going to notice.
Let's go 吠え面かきな Oh my haters
Let's go, cry your eyes out, oh my haters.
とりあえず浴びるわ拍手
For now, I'll just soak up the applause.
ほら見たことか にやけろ
See, I told you so! Now grin.
あー、べっちありがとう！
Ah, Baelz, thank you!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
お疲れ様でした！
Great job!
ばれる！
It's gonna get out!
こんちくわ
Konchikuwa
轟 はじめ
Hajime Todoroki
こん！ちくわ！こん！こん！ちくわ！こん！ちくわ！ぶんぶんぶん こん！ちくわ！こん！こん！ちくわ！こん！ちくわ！ちくわ！
Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Chikuwa! Bun-bun-bun Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Chikuwa! Chikuwa!
おっ おお おっ ふーん ふーん 泣いちゃうぞ ぴえん ぴえん おっ おお おっ すごい うーん すき おっ おお おっ 泣いちゃうぞ ぴえん ぴえん 泣いちゃうぞ 泣いちゃうぞ
Oh! Oh! Oh! Hmm Hmm I'm gonna cry Pien Pien Oh! Oh! Oh! Amazing Hmm Like Oh! Oh! Oh! I'm gonna cry Pien Pien I'm gonna cry I'm gonna cry
ごみゃん
Gomyan
こん！ちくわ！こん！こん！ちくわ！こん！ちくわ！最終手段抱いてやる こん！ちくわ！こん！こん！ちくわ！こん！ちくわ！こん！こん！ちくわ！
Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Chikuwa! Last resort, I'll embrace you Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa!
ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！あい！あい！げんき！あい！カツォでき仮想敵？カツォでき仮想敵？カツォでき仮想敵か あぁ仮想敵か ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！あい！あい！げんき！あい！
Pya! Pya! Pya! Pya! Ai! Ai! Energetic! Ai! Katsuo-deki imaginary enemy? Katsuo-deki imaginary enemy? Katsuo-deki imaginary enemy? Ah, imaginary enemy? Pya! Pya! Pya! Pya! Ai! Ai! Energetic! Ai!
今を生きろよ
Live for the now!
なかれたら泣き返す 今を生きろよ やさしいじゃん えぇ 抱くかぁ こん！ちくわ！こん！こん！ちくわ！こん！ちくわ！こん！こん！こん！こん！ちくわ！
If you're made to cry, cry back! Live for the now! Aren't you kind? Well, shall I embrace you? Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa!
こん！ちくわ！こん！こん！ちくわ！こん！ちくわ！おわり！わぁ！
Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Chikuwa! The end! Wow!
あのーノエル先輩がね
Um, Noel-senpai...
ラップしてたんだよー
was rapping.
ちょっと対抗してみようかな
I think I'll try to compete with her a bit.
もうちょっと 韻踏めない気がするけど
I don't think I can rhyme much more, though.
もう頭まわんなくて
My brain isn't working anymore.
よし、これにするか！
Alright, let's go with this!
二日目！
Day two!
ノエルだんちょーに対抗！
Going against Noel Danchou!
うちがらっぷばんちょー！
I'm the Rap Bancho!
ラップでバトルしよーよー！
Let's have a rap battle!
うちがらっぷばんちょー！
I'm the Rap Bancho!
初テイムはぶんぶんてんちょー
First tame was Bunbun Tencho
初レイドであっけなく終了
First raid ended in a flash
その次テイムしたの
The next one I tamed
アルゲンなんだよー
Was an Argentavis!
トワさんとフブキさんで
With Towa-san and Fubuki-san
大冒険なYO！
It's a big adventure, YO!
ビーバーとっこう！セメント大量！
Beaver suicide mission! Tons of cement!
大成功で終わったYO！
Ended in a big success, YO!
もっと強くなるばんちょー
Bancho's gonna get even stronger
うぃあー
We are
おーいノエルおめぇ負けてんぞ！
Hey Noel, you're losing!
時間がなさすぎてラップできなかった、みじかモーダよ！
I didn't have enough time to rap, so it's a short mode!
おいヤバイ、やめてよ、日記でラップバトル始めないでよ
Hey, wait, stop, don't start a rap battle with a diary
全然いいけど
Even though it's totally fine
ラップバトルしよーね！
Let's have a rap battle!
二日目！
Day two!
ノエルだんちょーに対抗！
Going against Noel Danchou!
うちがらっぷばんちょー！
I'm the Rap Bancho!
ラップでバトルしよーよー！
Let's have a rap battle!
うちがらっぷばんちょー！
I'm the Rap Bancho!
初テイムはぶんぶんてんちょー
First tame was Bunbun Tencho
初レイドであっけなく終了
First raid ended in a flash
その次テイムしたの
The next one I tamed
アルゲンなんだよー
Was an Argentavis!
トワさんとフブキさんで
With Towa-san and Fubuki-san
大冒険なYO！
It's a big adventure, YO!
ビーバーとっこう！セメント大量！
Beaver suicide mission! Tons of cement!
大成功で終わったYO！
Ended in a big success, YO!
もっと強くなるばんちょー
Bancho's gonna get even stronger
はい。ばんちょーの勝利、おめでとう。
Yes. Bancho's victory, congratulations.
I'm Koseki Bijou!
アイム 轟はじめ
I'm Todoroki Hajime
Boom Boom Boom! ぶんぶんぶん
Boom Boom Boom! Boom boom boom
Okey. はじめまして
Okey. Nice to meet you
今日は一緒に歌おう！Let's go!
Today, let's sing together! Let's go!
はじめ, cool! Yeah! Thank you, thank you!
Hajime, cool! Yeah! Thank you, thank you!
アイム ばんちょー Yeah Bancho yeah
I'm Bancho, yeah, Bancho, yeah
We were cool, right? あーくーる おーけぃ？
We were cool, right? Are we cool, okay?
Very very happy! ベリベリハッピー Thank you
Very very happy! Very very happy! Thank you
Can you say something for me?
Sticking out your gyatt for Nerizzler
なに、なに、なに！？
What, what, what!?
You're so Bau bau
Ok, You're so Biboo tax
I just wanna be your Shiori
Yeay! She said the thing!
聞いてー、聞いてーよもー
Listen, please listen
ボロボロ
I'm a mess
いまフワモコが、ばんちょー先生の所に向かってます、オーバー！
Fuwawa and Mococo are heading to Bancho-sensei's place now, over!
ばんちょー先生だー！
It's Bancho-sensei!
ばんちょー先生、いま持ってます、持たれてます
Bancho-sensei, holding now, being held
次はちょっとつめたいけど、がまんしてね
Next is a bit cold, but please bear with it
わ！つめたい！おへそにつめたい！
Wa! Cold! Cold on the belly button!
OKじゃあ、次はハートマッサージね
OK then, next is a heart massage
ハートマッサージ？マッサージ！
Heart massage? Massage!
これで大丈夫かなー！げんきになったー！
Is it okay now? I'm feeling better!
これからも病院がんばろうねー！
Let's keep doing our best at the hospital!
殴り合いますか？
Shall we trade blows?
あ、殴り合う？いいよ。ちょっといま溜まってるわ。
Oh, trade blows? Sure. I've got some built-up energy right now.
溜まってるｗ やめてｗ
Built-up? lol stop it lol
まあ久々にやるからね、ちょーできるか
Well, it's been a while, so let's see if I can do it
イクゾッ！
Here I go!
勝つ！ 勝つ！
Win! Win!
やめろー！ やめてー！
Stop it! Stop!
おれの勝ち！
My win!
完全勝利！
Complete victory!
ボール持って モチュッ
Hold the ball, mochu
ポイッ ビュイ〜 ホイッ
Throw! Pyui~ hoi!
チョイナチョ チョイ
Choinacho choi
ビュイ〜 えいっ えいっ
Pyui~ ei! ei!
Yes, I do.
ぶんぶんぶーん ばんちょー
Bun bun bun, Bancho
ぶんぶんぶーん...
Bun bun bun...
轟はじめです
I'm Todoki Hajime
またの名を ただの甘えん坊だ
Also known as just a spoiled brat
白銀ノエル またの名を 牛丼太郎だ
Shirogane Noel, also known as Gyudon Taro
よろしくな
Nice to meet ya
なん、なんなんだこのゲーム
Wha... what's with this game?
気合いじゃどうにもならんかったか
Guess fighting spirit wasn't enough, huh?
どうも、もるでちおです。
Hello, I'm Mordechio.
でび様に負けたので
Since I lost to Debi-sama,
今からでび様考案の うんちぷりぷりだんすをします
I'll now perform the Unchi Puri Puri dance proposed by Debi-sama.
うんちゃ ぷりやぷりや うんちゃ ぷりやぷりや
Uncha puriya puriya, uncha puriya puriya
異界の扉 開かれ中から来た
Coming from the opened gate of another world,
轟はじめ またの名を
Todoki Hajime, also known as
はじはじはじめ
Haji-Haji-Hajime,
よろしく
nice to meet you.
悪魔の中から来た
Coming from among the demons,
でびでび・でびる またの名を
Debidebi Debiru, also known as
うんちうんちうんち
Unchi Unchi Unchi.
はじめまして ありがとうございまーす 来てくだすって
Nice to meet you. Thank you very much for coming.
じゃあ今度は僕が踊ってって言ったら踊ってくれる？
Then, will you dance if I tell you to next time?
ダンス！ ぷりぷりダンス
Dance! Puri-puri dance.
またね また遊んでくだすぁい
Bye! Please play with me again.
また遊んでやるよ
I'll play with you again.
やったー！ せーのっ
Yay! One, two...
おつもるでちおー
Otsumordechio!
わあー、すごい楽しいコラボだったー。
Wow, that was such a fun collaboration!
あ、ちょっカメラちゃん、こっちこっちー。
Ah, wait, Camera-chan, over here, over here!
こっちこっちー。
Over here, over here!
いや、すごい楽しかった。
Man, that was so much fun.
あ、ちょ、トレンドも1位に入ったっちゅうことで
Ah, wait, since we even reached #1 on trends...
なんですかね？ありがとうございます！
...or something? Thank you so much!
ReGLOSSのみんなと、べーちゃんと、
With everyone from ReGLOSS, Bae-chan,
ぺこら先輩と、ビジュ先輩と、フワモコ先輩と、
Pekora-senpai, Bijou-senpai, Fuwamoco-senpai,
ノエル先輩と、でびちゃんというね...
Noel-senpai, and Debi-chan...
豪華10名のゲストが来てくれました！嬉しいー。
...a gorgeous lineup of 10 guests came! I'm so happy!
あの最後のやつは、はじめの『やる気出ないソング』を作ってくれた
For that last part, the one who made my 'No Motivation Song',
小玉代先生のこれまでの作品をメドレーにしてもらいました。
Odamayo-sensei, had her previous works turned into a medley.
可愛いメドレー、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for the cute medley.
このメドレー以外にもね、いろんな作品作ってるのでぜひ色々見てください。
She's made many other works too, so please check them out.
もう本当に先輩も同期もみんな来てくれて...
Really, seniors and colleagues all came...
にじさんじさんからでびちゃんもね、来てくれて。本当嬉しい。
...and even Debi-chan from Nijisanji came. I'm so happy.
またコラボして欲しいなー。
I want to collab again!
はい、ということで。
Alright then.
皆さん、どうですか？
Everyone, what do you think?
おちんちくごりんて言うな！いつも通り可愛いだろう。
Don't call me 'Ochinchikugorin'! I'm cute as always, right?
ま、でもね、ちょっとこれからまたダンスを披露したいので...
Well, but, I want to perform another dance now, so...
ちょっとね、ダンス見えやすいようにストレッチしてくるわ。
I'll go stretch a bit to make the dance easier to see.
ちょっと待ってて。ちょっと待ってて。
Wait a second. Wait a second.
体固くなってたわ。伸びた伸びた。
My body was getting stiff. Stretched out.
ということでね、次の曲に行きたいと思います。
So, I'd like to move on to the next song.
聴いてください、ワールドイズマイン。
Please listen to: World is Mine.
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world
そう言う お熱い心へ
To such a hot heart
Hey!
よれ！
Here we go!
ワールドイズマイン
作詞・作曲：ryo (supercell)
World is Mine
Lyrics & Composition: ryo (supercell)
その一
Number one
いつもと違う髪型に気がつくこと
Make sure you notice when my hairstyle is different from usual
その二
Number two
ちゃんと靴まで見ること いいね？
Make sure you look all the way down to my shoes, got it?
その三
Number three
私の一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
For every word I say, reply with three
わかったら右手がお留守なのを
If you understand, then do something about
何とかして！
how my right hand is feeling lonely!
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything
キミに心から思って欲しいの
I just want you to think from the bottom of your heart
かわいいって
that I'm cute
世界で一番おひめさま
I'm the number one princess in the world
気がついて ねえねえ
Notice me, hey, hey
待たせるなんて論外よ
Keeping me waiting is out of the question
私を誰だと思ってるの？
Who do you think I am?
もうなんだか
I'm starting to feel like
甘いものが食べたい！
I want to eat something sweet!
今すぐによ
Right this instant!
Check one, two!
欠点？ かわいいの間違いでしょ
Flaws? You must mean "cute," right?
文句は許しませんの
I won't allow any complaints
あのね、私の話ちゃんと聞いてる？ ちょっと...
Hey, are you listening to me? Wait...
あ、それとね 白いお馬さん 決まってるでしょ？
Oh, and also, a white horse is a given, right?
迎えに来て
Come pick me up
わかったら跪いて
If you understand, kneel down,
手を取って「おひめさま」って
take my hand, and call me "Princess"
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything
でもね 少しくらい叱ってくれたっていいのよ
But you know, it's okay to scold me just a little bit
世界で私だけの王子さま
You're my one and only prince in the world
気がついて ほらほら
Notice me, look, look
おててが空いてます
My hand is empty
無口で無愛想な王子さま
My silent and blunt prince
もう どうして！
Oh, why?!
気がついてよ早く
Hurry up and notice
絶対キミはわかってない！
You definitely don't understand!
わかってないわ...
You don't understand...
いちごの乗ったショートケーキ
Strawberry shortcake
こだわり卵のとろけるプリン
Melting pudding made with special eggs
みんな みんな 我慢します...
I'll endure them all, every single one...
わがままな子だと思わないで
Please don't think I'm a selfish girl
私だってやればできるもん
I can do it if I try
あとで後悔するわよ
You'll regret it later!
当然です！ だって私は
It's only natural! Because I am...
世界で一番おひめさま
the number one princess in the world
ちゃんと見ててよね
Make sure you're watching me
どこかに行っちゃうよ？
Or I'll go off somewhere, you know?
ふいに抱きしめられた 急に そんな ええっ？
You suddenly hugged me—just like that, out of nowhere? Eh?!
「轢かれる、危ないよ」
"You'll get hit, it's dangerous"
そう言ってそっぽ向くキミ
You say that and look away
こっちのが危ないわよ
You're the one who's more dangerous!
Oh!
Hey baby!
恋はイリュージョン
作詞：三森すずこ
作曲：矢野博康
Love is an Illusion
Lyrics: Suzuko Mimori
Composition: Hiroyasu Yano
街の灯りが滲んでる
The city lights are blurring
そっと手で触れそうな三日月
A crescent moon that looks like I could gently touch it
あなたに会える特別な
On this special night when I can see you
...じゃないわ
...it's not like that,
Yuppy Happy きらめくダイヤモンドで
Yuppy Happy, with sparkling diamonds.
いつもよりゆっくり
More slowly than usual,
いつもよりも早く
Faster than usual,
一緒にいたくて
I just want to be with you.
慣れないハイヒール
These unfamiliar high heels
よろめいちゃうから
make me stumble,
腕を貸して
so lend me your arm,
そのままで
just like that.
見え見えかしら
Is it so obvious?
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion,
少しロマンチック
a little romantic.
予想できないほど愛しかせて
Make me love you more than I could predict.
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion,
少しファンタスティック
a little fantastic.
隠しきれないこの胸のドキドキ
This heartbeat I can't hide.
瞳閉じてみたら
If I try closing my eyes,
シュワシュワシュワシュワ
fizz, fizz, fizz, fizz...
聞こえてくるでしょう
you can hear it, right?
映画のワンシーン
Like a scene from a movie,
みたいにキュンとする
it makes my heart flutter.
仕草リサーチ
Even if I research
してみても
your gestures,
あなたに会った瞬間
the moment I meet you,
全部曖昧
it all becomes vague.
揺れてるピンクサファイア
Swaying pink sapphire.
言葉より目覚めて
Awakening more than words,
目覚めより心で
with the heart more than awakening,
繋ぎ合っても
even if we connect.
慣れない静けさに
In this unfamiliar silence,
緊張しちゃうから
I get nervous,
微笑んで
so just smile,
そのままで
just like that.
手を繋ごうかしら
Should we hold hands?
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion,
甘いテンプテーション
sweet temptation.
予想できないほど愛しかせて
Make me love you more than I could predict.
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion,
甘いテンプテーション
sweet temptation.
隠しきれないこの胸のドキドキ
This heartbeat I can't hide.
シャンパンの泡のよう
Like champagne bubbles,
シュワシュワシュワシュワ
fizz, fizz, fizz, fizz...
弾けてるでしょう
it's popping, right?
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion,
少しロマンチック
a little romantic.
優しく手招き
A gentle beckoning,
ふとしたぬくもり
a sudden warmth.
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion,
かなりファンタスティック
quite fantastic.
隠しきれないこの胸のドキドキ
This heartbeat I can't hide.
瞳閉じてみたら
If I try closing my eyes,
シュワシュワシュワシュワ
fizz, fizz, fizz, fizz...
聞こえてくるでしょう
you can hear it, right?
いつまで子供のままでいる？
How long will you remain a child?
そんな言葉が降りかかる
Such words fall upon me.
黙って見てればいいんだ
I should just watch in silence.
笑って
Smile,
そう言ってやれ
and say so to them.
人生にはないんだ take2
There's no take 2 in life.
平凡でくだらない退屈
Boring and trivial boredom.
なれてごめん
I'm tired of it, sorry.
現実的な言葉なんかには耳を塞げ
Block your ears to realistic words.
ネバーランドに閉じこもって
Shutting myself in Neverland,
いつまでだって夢を語るんだ
I'll talk about dreams forever.
笑う奴には唾を吐け
Spit at those who laugh.
にっちもさっちもいかない程
Until there's no way out,
綺麗事に踊り踊らされ
being made to dance by beautiful words.
大人の言う常識なんてものは
Common sense that adults talk about,
丸めて捨てちまえ
just roll it up and throw it away.
ピーターパン症候群と
Even if I'm called a victim of
指を指され 罵られようが
Peter Pan Syndrome and abused,
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドを
I'll live on, imagining a
思い描いて生きていくんだ
fairy tale happy ending.
わーおー
Woah-oh
こっち指差して笑ってんだろ
You're pointing this way and laughing, aren't you?
好きに笑えよ それで別にいいさ
Laugh all you want, it's fine by me.
お前なんかにも お前らなんかに
To people like you... Yeah, to people like you,
何も言われたくない 黙って見てろ
I don't want to hear anything. Just shut up and watch.
やり直しのきかない人生 一度でいいチャンスをください
A life that can't be redone, please give me just one good chance.
掴んで離さない もう俺のものなんだ
I'll grab it and never let go, it's mine now.
ネバーランドの大気圏を 破って今夢を叶えるんだ
Break through the atmosphere of Neverland and make your dream come true now.
笑う奴など 蹴り飛ばせ
Kick away those who laugh at you.
打つ手はない残されてない ネガティブを押し付けてくんな
No moves left? Don't force your negativity on me.
大人のあんたも知らない世界を 俺は生きてるんだ
I'm living in a world even you adults don't know.
ピーターパン症候群と 思われたって馬鹿にされたって
Even if I'm thought to have Peter Pan Syndrome, even if I'm made fun of...
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドに 一直線に進んでいくんだ
I'll head straight for a happy ending like in a fairy tale.
夢の見過ぎと馬鹿にされた少年が
The story of a boy who was ridiculed
夢を掴む物語を
for dreaming too much, seizing his dream.
見事な逆転劇をこの手で 巻き起こせ 見せつけろ
Bring about a brilliant comeback with these hands! Show them!
にっちもさっちもいかないよ 綺麗事に踊らされ
I'm stuck in a bind, dancing to sugar-coated words.
大人の言う常識なんてものは 丸めて捨てちまえ
Things like 'common sense' adults talk about? Roll them up and throw them away!
ピーターパン症候群と 呼びたきゃ叫び散らしてろよ
If you want to call it Peter Pan Syndrome, then go ahead and scream it out.
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドを そう自ら掴み取るんだ
I'll seize a fairy-tale-like happy end with my own hands!
わーおー
Woah-oh
はい！
Yes!
えー、改め、はじめまして！
Um, once again, nice to meet you!
初めてタップに挑戦しました。声は、入りちょった？
I tried tap dancing for the first time. Was my voice picked up?
そして、えー、初めての歌枠で歌った、はじめの大好きな、えー、優里さんの『ピーターパン』でした！ありがとうございます！
And that was Yuuri-san's 'Peter Pan,' which I sang in my very first singing stream and which I love! Thank you!
次はオリ曲を2曲やっていきます！
Next, I'll be doing two original songs!
えっ、オリ曲2曲？えっ、そんな持ってたっけ、轟はじめ？
Eh, two original songs? Wait, did Hajime Todoroki have that many?
『Countach』そして、新曲が出ます！
'Countach' and then... a new song is coming out!
2曲続けて聴いてください！
Please listen to these two songs in a row!
それでは聴いてください、『Countach』！
Now, please listen to 'Countach'!
Countach
何のため頑張るの 報われない Day by Day
What am I working hard for? Day by day without reward.
結局正直者が 道化師で踊る残像
In the end, the honest ones are just afterimages of clowns dancing.
狡賢く生きてるあの子 懐に舞い込む
That kid living craftily, slipping into favor...
優等生でしょ
You're a model student, aren't you?
アブラカタブラ 開けるよパンドラ
Abracadabra, I'm opening Pandora's box.
抑えきれないのさ 歌うかサンドラ
I can't hold it back, shall I sing, Sandra?
シェイクスピアも真っ青 暴れ馬で降臨 カーニバル
Shakespeare would turn pale. Descending like a wild horse, it's a carnival.
Everybody gonna put your hand clap clap まだ見ぬ世界 飛び込め 3 2 1
Everybody gonna put your hand clap clap. Dive into the unknown world, 3 2 1!
上がれ壇上へ 体揺らして
Get up on the stage and move your body!
既成概念 あるがままぶち壊せ
Break down those preconceived notions just as they are!
上がれ壇上へ 体揺らして
Get up on the stage and move your body!
既成概念 あるがままぶち壊せ
Break down those preconceived notions just as they are!
Countach 最上級の Countach
Countach! The ultimate Countach!
Countach 一心不乱で Countach
Countach! With focused concentration, Countach!
Countach 火蓋を Countach
Countach! Fire the opening shot, Countach!
Countach 難度だって Countach
Countach! Whatever the difficulty, Countach!
息を潜めて自分を 殺すのはもう慣れてんの
I'm used to holding my breath and killing my true self.
存在価値 存在証明なんて どうでもええわ
Worth or proof of existence, I don't care about any of that.
宴ならエンドレス 今宵突破らえよボーダーレス
If it's a banquet, it's endless. Tonight, break through and make it borderless.
神の雷浴びちゃって Perfect 弾け飛んで理想郷
Bathed in the lightning of God, perfect! Bursting into a utopia.
アブラカタブラ 開けるよパンドラ
Abracadabra, I'm opening Pandora's box.
抑えきれないのさ
I can't hold it back.
ハイレゾサンダー
High-res thunder
半端なカモフラージュ
Half-baked camouflage
本能的で十分混ざり合う
Mixing well enough instinctively
Everybody gonna put your hands clap clap
明日のことは忘れろ 3, 2, 1
Forget about tomorrow, 3, 2, 1
叫べてっぺんへ
Shout out to the peak
声を枯らして
Until your voice runs dry
君だけの人生
Your one and only life
楽しまなきゃ損じゃない
It's a waste if you don't enjoy it, right?
叫べてっぺんへ
Shout out to the peak
声を枯らして
Until your voice runs dry
君だけの人生
Your one and only life
楽しまなきゃ損じゃない
It's a waste if you don't enjoy it, right?
6PM 鳴るアラーム
The 6 PM alarm goes off
アバレウマ並みのクールなカーニバル
A cool carnival like a wild horse
Everybody gonna put your hands clap clap
まだ見ぬ世界へ飛び込め 3, 2, 1
Dive into a world yet unseen, 3, 2, 1
Are you ready?
上がれ壇上へ
Rise up onto the stage
体揺らして
Shake your body
ほら規制はない
Look, there are no restrictions
あるがままぶち壊せ
Destroy it all just as it is
上がれ壇上へ
Rise up onto the stage
体揺らして
Shake your body
ほら規制はない
Look, there are no restrictions
あるがままぶち壊せ
Destroy it all just as it is
カウンタック
Countach
最上級のカウンタック
The highest class Countach
カウンタック
Countach
一心不乱にカウンタック
One-mindedly Countach
Into your Countach
何度だってカウンタック
As many times as it takes, Countach
バンザイ無能な命に
Banzai to this incompetent life
くだらないよ紛い物だってモラリチュード
It's worthless, even if it's a fake moralitude
BANZAI
作詞・作曲：マサ 編曲：田中タブラ
Lyrics/Composition: Masa, Arrangement: Tanaka Tabra
偶然恋してるようなもん
It's like I'm falling in love by chance
不条理浴びながら僕は歩く
I walk while being showered in absurdity
才能はゼロ
Talent is zero
どうにかなっちゃってるキャラ
A character who's gone a bit crazy
感性はノー
Sensibility is no
だったな Oh Oh Oh
It was like that, oh oh oh
愛にもたれた言葉で心拍数
Heart rate with words leaning on love
生きてくほど胸は沈んでいく
The more I live, the more my heart sinks
どうなってんだろうな
I wonder what's going on
この音が揺れるの
This sound is shaking
かいつまんでもしょうがねえ
Summarizing it won't help
汗かき稼ぐお金はどんだけ？
How much money earned through sweat?
ああだこうだ そんなもんか
This and that, is that all?
五月蝿えな
How noisy
バンザイ無能な命に
Banzai to this incompetent life
空回ってく脳を満たしてくれ
Fill up my brain that's spinning in circles
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't draw any future blueprints
くだらないよ紛い物だってそれ
It's worthless, even if it's a fake thing
半端者なら Nutty Tune
If you're a half-baked person, Nutty Tune
朱色になって僕は思い通り
Turning vermillion, I'm just as I wished
太陽系で足踏まった
Stepped on a foot in the solar system
罵言雑言インベーダー
Abuse and slander invader
足が止まってるシューゲイザー
A shoegazer whose feet have stopped
死にそうでもギリですか
Even if you're dying, is it just barely?
のらりくらり交わすわ
Dodging aimlessly
はじめまして神様
Nice to meet you, God
もし救われるのなら 吐けるわ今から
If I can be saved, I'll spit it out starting now
Got down Got down 揺るがぬ Get down
Got down, got down, unshakeable get down
飲み込んだ背徳が君を狂わしてんだ
The immorality I swallowed is driving you crazy
待ったもんじゃ驚かねえ
I won't be surprised by something that waited
汗かき生きろ 最後も呆気ねえ
Live sweating, the end is also anticlimactic
なんだかんだ そんなもんさ
This and that, it's just like that
虚しいわな
It's empty, isn't it
バンザイ無能な命に
Banzai to this incompetent life
空回ってく脳を満たしてくれ
Fill up my brain that's spinning in circles
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't draw any future blueprints
くだらないよ紛い物だってそれ
It's worthless, even if it's a fake thing
半端者なら Nutty Tune
If you're a half-baked person, Nutty Tune
朱色になって僕は思い通り
Turning vermillion, I'm just as I wished
HORNS RIOT
作曲: Yusuke Orita / Goushi Nishizaki
Composition: Yusuke Orita / Goushi Nishizaki
はい！ということで、宣伝番長がいってきまーす！
Yes! So, Promo Bancho is heading out!
轟はじめ生誕記念2025...
Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2025...
轟はじめ生誕記念2025 フルセット
Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2025 Full Set
...フルセットはこんな感じでーす！
...the full set looks like this!
ひとつずつ紹介していきます！
I'll introduce them one by one!
ひとつめ、アクリルパネル。
First, the acrylic panel.
アクリルパネル
Acrylic Panel
おもちチャウダー先生の可愛いイラストとなって、オーロラ加工になってます。
It features a cute illustration by Omochi Chowder-sensei and has an aurora finish.
なにやら、ジャケットをご試着しているようです。
It looks like I'm trying on a jacket.
めちゃめちゃ可愛い！
So cute!
ふたつめ、BANCHOアクリルキーホルダー。
Second, the BANCHO acrylic keychains.
BANCHOアクリルキーホルダー
BANCHO Acrylic Keychains
おもちチャウダー先生のブンブンBANCHOのイラストです！
These are illustrations of Bunbun BANCHO by Omochi Chowder-sensei!
三つ繋げてもひとつずつでも使えます。
You can use them linked together or individually.
カラビナは雷の形になってます！
The carabiner is shaped like a lightning bolt!
ぜひカバンとかに付けてみてね！
Please try attaching them to your bags!
三つめ、BANCHOナイロンジャケット。
Third, the BANCHO nylon jacket.
BANCHOナイロンジャケット
BANCHO Nylon Jacket
こちらは実際に実物で色味をチェックして、使いやすいデザインにしました！
I checked the colors of the actual item and made it a user-friendly design!
おもちチャウダー先生のミニBANCHOのイラストと、
It has an illustration of mini BANCHO by Omochi Chowder-sensei, and...
表にははじめの考えたBANCHOのロゴがついてます！
the front has the BANCHO logo I designed!
チャック、雷の形になってます。
The zipper is shaped like a lightning bolt.
キービジュアルのはじめとお揃いのデザインです！
It's the same design as me in the key visual!
最後、シチュエーションボイス。
Lastly, the situation voice.
ボイス
Voice
ナイロンジャケットにまつわるボイスです！
It's a voice recording related to the nylon jacket!
よかったら合わせて聴いてください！
Please listen to it along with the jacket!
今回、フルセット購入特典は二つあります！
There are two bonuses for purchasing the full set this time!
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
ひとつめ、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイド！
First, a signed instax-style bromide!
枚数無制限になってます！
There's no limit on the number of copies!
このライブが良かったなーと思ってくださったら、次回以降のライブの励みになるのでぜひよろしくお願いします！
If you enjoyed this live show, it would be a great encouragement for future shows, so please consider it!
ふたつめ、
Second,
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PRカード HBD24-051「轟はじめ」
hololive Official Card Game PR Card HBD24-051 "Todoroki Hajime"
オフィシャルショップにて購入された方限定で、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使えるカードが1枚付きます！
exclusively for those who purchase from the official shop, you'll get one card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game!
カードの詳細や遊び方については公式ホームページを見てください！
Please check the official website for card details and how to play!
以上、グッズ紹介でした！いきっちゃ！
That's all for the merch introduction! Let's go!
あ、まだまだ踊っていくので、ぜひ最後まで見てください！
Ah, I'm still going to dance, so please watch until the end!
それじゃ、いけ！はじめダンスアタック！
Alright, go! Hajime Dance Attack!
えい！
Ei!
ふっふー！
Fuh-fuh!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
あ、みんな！こんちわー！
Ah, everyone! Hello!
あ、こっちのみんなもこんちわー！
Ah, everyone over here too, hello!
え、クラップ！
Eh, clap!
え、え、え、え、え！
Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ありがとー！本当に、本当にライブ来てくれてありがとねー！
Thank you! Thank you so, so much for coming to the live show!
はい！ということで、みなさん本当にありがとうございました！
Yes! So, everyone, thank you very much!
えー、このあと21時、新曲『バンザイ』のMVプレミア公開！そしてグッズ販売も開始されます！
Uh, at 21:00 after this, the MV for the new song "Banzai" will have its premiere! And merch sales will also start!
そしてそのあとは、メンバー限定のアンコールライブもあります！
And after that, there will be an encore live show for members only!
わあ、時間ぴったり！うおー、嬉しい！
Wow, perfect timing! Whoa, I'm so happy!
あのトレンドもね、ありがとうございました！
And thank you for the trending topic too!
本当にみんなありがとー！おつかめー、ありがとー！
Thank you so much, everyone! Otsukame, thank you!
みなたん！！ いつも応援ありがとう！！
Minatan!! Thank you for always supporting me!!
ずっと夢だった主役LIVEができて本当に幸せです！
I'm so happy to have the solo LIVE I dreamed of!
一回一回のステージをこれまで以上にパワフルにして、
I'll make every stage more powerful than ever,
毎回あっと驚かせてみせるから！
and I'll surprise you every time!
First Starring Role
TODOROKI HAJIME BIRTHDAY LIVE 2025